. .
The dust has settled on the keys A whisper in the
willow trees I see a face I used to know In a mirror
from long ago The glass is silvered, cracked and
grey The shadows of a yesterday
Turn the page and let the cold hours fade In the
mirrors of the lives we make We are looking
through a broken lens Finding where the circle
ends Ambigens Mirrors of yesterday
You trace the outline of the frame And softly
speak a fatted name The hallway echoes with the
sound Of orchestras beneath the ground Oh, in
the glass, the light is new And I'm standing here
with you
Turn the page and let the cold house fade In the
mirrors of the lives we make We are looking
through a broken lens Finding where the circle
ends And begins Mirrors of yesterday Eyes
all we have Eyes all we keep Awakening from
twenty years of sleep
Bye!
Turn the page and let the callouts fade In the
mirrors of the lives we've made We are looking
through a broken lens Finding where the circle
ends and begins Mirrors of yesterday
Mirrors of yesterday